Alien Tornado is a science fiction, action, thriller film directed by Jeff Burr.
Aliens attack Earth with deadly electrical tornadoes, and it’s up to a farmer, his smart
high-school daughter and a tornado blogger to thwart the horrific invasion.
Gail Curtis, played by Kari Wührer.
Kelly Walker, played by Stacey Asaro.
Judd Walker, played by Jeff Fahey.
Street Fighter (uncredited), played by Chip Haw.
Armstrong, played by David Jensen.
DJ (uncredited), played by Mike Kimmel.
Alien: Romulus is a 2024 science fiction horror film directed by Fede
Álvarez, who co-wrote the script with Rodo Sayagues.
It is the seventh installment in the Alien film series, set
between the events of Alien (1979) and Aliens (1986).
The film stars Cailee Spaeny, David Jonsson, Archie Renaux, Isabela Merced, Spike Fearn, and Aileen Wu as six downtrodden young space
colonists who encounter hostile creatures while scavenging a derelict space station in which they plan to navigate to another planet.
At CinemaCon in April 2019, 20th Century Studios (then-named 20th
Century Fox) announced plans to produce future Alien films.
Álvarez was attached as director in March 2022, and
Spaeny joined as the lead later that year.
Filming took place from March to July 2023.
Alien: Romulus premiered in Los Angeles on August 12, 2024, and was theatrically
released in the United States by 20th Century Studios on August 16.
The film grossed $350.9 million worldwide and received
generally positive reviews from critics.
It received several industry nominations, namely for its technical aspects,
including an Academy Award nomination for Best Visual Effects.
A sequel is in development.
The film explores themes of tornado, alien, alien invasion.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.